<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reinforcement Learning on Quang Chiem</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/reinforcement-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reinforcement Learning on Quang Chiem</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/reinforcement-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Typesetting – AI-based Newspaper Placement Tool for the Japanese market.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/mti-p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/mti-p1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevance to the Business:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Applied machine learning, deep learning and data analytics expertise to develop a sophisticated typesetting tool.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Targeted specifically for Japanese newspapers, aimed at enhancing efficiency, quality of layout design and cost reduction.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accomplishments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Secured a patent for the Typesetting API.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Delivered a Proof of Concept (PoC) to renowned companies like Toshiba and Fujitsu.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transferable Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of state of the art machine learning methodologies and their business applications in python (sklearn, pytorch, flask, fastapi)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of IT and Cluster technologies: Docker, Gitlab.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Analytical skill, Data visualization, Constraint Programming and Deep Reinforcement Learning (Proximal Policy Optimization).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leadership, project management, and problem-solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typesetting - AI-driven solution to automate the labour-intensive process of newspaper article arrangement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/blog/typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/blog/typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;The typesetting project aimed to create an AI-driven solution to automate the labor-intensive process of newspaper article arrangement, addressing several critical challenges. Manual typesetting is notoriously time-consuming and stressful, often leading to inconsistent layouts and potential human errors. These issues not only hinder productivity but also limit the ability to explore diverse solutions for optimal newspaper design. By leveraging Assistive AI, this project seeks to significantly reduce the manual workload, enhance operational efficiency, and ensure consistent output quality. The successful application of this technology in typesetting showcases its potential transferability to other industries facing similar manual challenges, offering a scalable solution for improving efficiency and reducing human error across various fields.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
