<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GenAI on Quang Chiem</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/genai/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GenAI on Quang Chiem</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/genai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AI Avatar Generator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/self-p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/self-p1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- &lt;img src=&#34;https://ars.els-cdn.com/content/image/3-s2.0-B9780128243497000153-f08-34-9780128243497.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;MarineGEO circle logo&#34; style=&#34;height: 100%; width:100%;&#34;/&gt; --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ars.els-cdn.com/content/image/3-s2.0-B9780128243497000153-f08-34-9780128243497.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;MarineGEO circle logo&#34; title=&#34;MarineGEO logo&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevance to the Business:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leveraged my expertise in Deep Learning and Gen AI to develop AI-based tools for generating avatar for individual creators and influencers. The tool offers a new medium to express creativity and help to maintain a consistent and engaging online presence.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accomplishments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;An Application Programming Interface for AI Avatar generation tool.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transferable Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of image processing, data preprocessing, and model evaluation techniques&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Solid Understanding of Generative Deep Learning (Gan and Diffusion models),&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Question Answering System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/self-p4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/self-p4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- &lt;img src=&#34;https://ars.els-cdn.com/content/image/3-s2.0-B9780128243497000153-f08-34-9780128243497.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;MarineGEO circle logo&#34; style=&#34;height: 100%; width:100%;&#34;/&gt; --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://lilianweng.github.io/posts/2020-10-29-odqa/QA-summary.png&#34; alt=&#34;Question Answering System&#34; title=&#34;Question Answering System&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevance to the Business:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leveraged my expertise in deep learning and Natural Language Processing (NLP) to develop tools for enhancing efficient information retrieval in today&amp;rsquo;s data-driven environment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Targeted at business entities who improve customer support and productivity by automating the extraction of valuable insights from their vast databases.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accomplishments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Delivered an attractive Proof of Concept (PoC) to MTI and some private clients, showcasing practical applications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transferable Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short-term Hail Nowcast Using AI for Extreme Weather Events</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/mti-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/mti-p2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevance to the Business:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leveraged my expertise in machine learning, deep learning, and data analytics to pioneer the development of an innovative AI-driven tool for short-term weather forecasting, with a specific focus on predicting hailstorms.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Targeted diverse spectrum of Japanese companies, primarily targeting the insurance and car dealership sectors, aimed at elevating risk assessment capabilities by providing exceptionally accurate forecasts. This enhancement in risk assessment holds particular significance for the insurance sector, where weather-related events can exert substantial financial implications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accomplishments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Unpredictable: AI-Powered Weather Forecasting for Severe Events in Japan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/weather/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:justify&#34;&gt;&#xA;&amp;emsp; This project focuses on developing an advanced AI-based system for early detection of extreme weather events in Japan. By leveraging cutting-edge machine learning algorithms and analyzing vast amounts of historical weather data, this system aims to:&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improve accuracy and lead time:&lt;/strong&gt; Provide more accurate and timely predictions of severe weather events, such as intense rainfall, strong winds, and heavy snowfall.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhance early warning systems:&lt;/strong&gt; Empower weather information service providers to issue more precise and timely warnings to the public, allowing for swift evacuation and precautionary measures.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reduce human error:&lt;/strong&gt; Minimize the impact of human error in weather forecasting by automating data analysis and prediction processes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enable proactive risk management:&lt;/strong&gt; Equip individuals, businesses, and government agencies with the necessary information to proactively assess risks and implement effective mitigation strategies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;#demo&#34;&gt; &#xA;        &lt;button class=&#34;button&#34; style=&#34;color:red&#34;&gt;See demonstration !!!&lt;/button&gt; &#xA;    &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-key-benefits-of-this-ai-powered-weather-prediction-system&#34;&gt;I. Key benefits of this AI-powered weather prediction system&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Save lives:&lt;/strong&gt; Enable timely evacuations and reduce casualties during severe weather events.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimize property damage:&lt;/strong&gt; Allow for proactive measures to protect homes, businesses, and critical infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support informed decision-making:&lt;/strong&gt; Provide valuable data for emergency responders, disaster relief agencies, and government officials.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhance public awareness:&lt;/strong&gt; Raise public awareness about the dangers of severe weather and promote preparedness.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This project represents a significant step towards a more proactive and data-driven approach to weather forecasting in Japan. By harnessing the power of AI, we can build a more resilient and safer society, better prepared to face the challenges of the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
