<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Constrained Programming on Quang Chiem</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/constrained-programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Constrained Programming on Quang Chiem</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 14:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/constrained-programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionizing Newspaper Design: How AI is Automating Typesetting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:justify&#34;&gt;&#xA;&amp;emsp; The newsroom is a whirlwind of activity, with editors juggling deadlines, reporters chasing stories, and designers wrestling with stacks of paper and design software. Among these challenges, the process of typesetting – arranging articles, images, and advertisements on the page – stands out as a particularly time-consuming and labor-intensive task. But what if this critical step could be streamlined and enhanced with the power of artificial intelligence?&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;#demo&#34;&gt; &#xA;        &lt;button style=&#34;color:red&#34;&gt;See demonstration !!!&lt;/button&gt; &#xA;    &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-the-pain-points-of-traditional-typesetting&#34;&gt;I. The Pain Points of Traditional Typesetting&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:justify&#34;&gt;&#xA;&amp;emsp; Traditionally, typesetting is a manual and often tedious process. Designers meticulously arrange elements on the page, considering factors like headline size, image placement, and column widths. This meticulous work is prone to human error, leading to inconsistencies in layout and potential for missed deadlines. The pressure to meet tight deadlines adds to the stress, hindering creativity and the ability to explore diverse and innovative design solutions. The process is illustrated in the Figure below&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Typical typesetting process used in newspaper company&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
