<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weather on Chiem Tri Quang</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/weather/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weather on Chiem Tri Quang</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/weather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hailstorm Forecast Using AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/mti-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/mti-p2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:justify&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;relevance-to-the-business&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevance to the Business:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leveraged my expertise in machine learning, deep learning, and data analytics to pioneer the development of an innovative AI-driven tool for short-term weather forecasting, with a specific focus on predicting hailstorms.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Targeted diverse spectrum of Japanese companies, primarily targeting the insurance and car dealership sectors, aimed at elevating risk assessment capabilities by providing exceptionally accurate forecasts. This enhancement in risk assessment holds particular significance for the insurance sector, where weather-related events can exert substantial financial implications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;accomplishments&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accomplishments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Developed a Short-term Hail Nowcast prototype, surpassing the accuracy of the Japan Meteorological Agency&amp;rsquo;s (JMA) forecast system (72% vs. 55%).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Delivered a compelling Proof of Concept (PoC) to MS&amp;amp;AD insurance group, showcasing practical applications and superior forecasting capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;transferable-skills&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transferable Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Analytical skills and Quantitative Analysis, Data visualization&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Geneartive AI&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Weather and Radar Meteorology.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leadership, project management, and problem-solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;responsibilities&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Led a data science team, ensuring collaboration between data scientists and industry experts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mentor the junior team members and support them with technical issues.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Translated specific needs of stakeholders into an optimized deep learning model.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;challenges-and-difficulties&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Challenges and Difficulties:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Required a deep understanding of meteorological data and generative deep learning techniques to provide accurate forecasts in a short time frame.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;feedback-and-endorsements&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feedback and Endorsements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Positive feedback from stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;context&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Context:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive background in deep learning and data analytics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Commitment to projects with direct business relevance, contributing to industry advancements.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Personalized Travel Recommendation Systems: Leveraging User Preferences and Destination Connections</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/graph_recom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/graph_recom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/comming_soon.gif&#34; alt=&#34;COMING SOON&#34; title=&#34;COMMING SOON&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Unpredictable: AI-Powered Weather Forecasting for Hailstorm in Japan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/weather/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:justify&#34;&gt;&#xA;&amp;emsp; The skies over Japan often paint a dramatic picture, with thunderstorms booming, strong winds blowing, and hailstones crashing onto rooftops and fields. During this severe weather, communities prepare for the worst, farmers try to save their crops, and emergency services get ready to help. However, predicting hail – a weather event that can cause serious damage to people and property – has always been a difficult and uncertain task. But what if this challenge could be tackled with precision and foresight using the power of Artificial Intelligence?&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  This post provide general information of a Hail Forecast system used in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mti.co.jp/?p=33519&#34;&gt;Hail Alert Service in Japan provided by MTI &lt;/a&gt; By harnessing state-of-the-art machine learning algorithms and analyzing extensive historical weather radar data, this system aims to:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
