<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Quang Chiem</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Quang Chiem</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 14:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionizing Newspaper Design: How AI is Automating Typesetting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:justify&#34;&gt;&#xA;&amp;emsp; The newsroom is a whirlwind of activity, with editors juggling deadlines, reporters chasing stories, and designers wrestling with stacks of paper and design software. Among these challenges, the process of typesetting – arranging articles, images, and advertisements on the page – stands out as a particularly time-consuming and labor-intensive task. But what if this critical step could be streamlined and enhanced with the power of artificial intelligence?&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;#demo&#34;&gt; &#xA;        &lt;button style=&#34;color:red&#34;&gt;See demonstration !!!&lt;/button&gt; &#xA;    &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-the-pain-points-of-traditional-typesetting&#34;&gt;I. The Pain Points of Traditional Typesetting&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:justify&#34;&gt;&#xA;&amp;emsp; Traditionally, typesetting is a manual and often tedious process. Designers meticulously arrange elements on the page, considering factors like headline size, image placement, and column widths. This meticulous work is prone to human error, leading to inconsistencies in layout and potential for missed deadlines. The pressure to meet tight deadlines adds to the stress, hindering creativity and the ability to explore diverse and innovative design solutions. The process is illustrated in the Figure below&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Typical typesetting process used in newspaper company&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forcing Visits to use SSL</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/force-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/force-ssl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter whether it&amp;rsquo;s a CakePHP app for a client, your own personal CMS, or any other web based application. &lt;strong&gt;If your passing around passwords or other sensitive info you should really implement SSL.&lt;/strong&gt; SSL provides 2 main perks to your visitors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;First it encrypts all communication that flies across the web. This prevents curious or devious billies from getting your secrets.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Secondly it ensures to the user that your server is in fact who it claims, and not a nasty &amp;lsquo;man in the middle&amp;quot; attack.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Finally it gives your site that touch of class&amp;hellip;. which of course a classy person like yourself relies on.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you implement SSL certificates on your server you&amp;rsquo;ll want to &lt;strong&gt;require secure connections&lt;/strong&gt; using Apache&amp;rsquo;s rewrite module. Now I won&amp;rsquo;t dwell on the creation and signing of certificates, its already well documented.  If your just starting out though,heres a few links I recommend;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
