<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deep Learning on Quang Chiem</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/deep-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deep Learning on Quang Chiem</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 14:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/deep-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hailstorm Forecast Using AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/mti-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/mti-p2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:justify&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;relevance-to-the-business&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevance to the Business:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leveraged my expertise in machine learning, deep learning, and data analytics to pioneer the development of an innovative AI-driven tool for short-term weather forecasting, with a specific focus on predicting hailstorms.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Targeted diverse spectrum of Japanese companies, primarily targeting the insurance and car dealership sectors, aimed at elevating risk assessment capabilities by providing exceptionally accurate forecasts. This enhancement in risk assessment holds particular significance for the insurance sector, where weather-related events can exert substantial financial implications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;accomplishments&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accomplishments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Developed a Short-term Hail Nowcast prototype, surpassing the accuracy of the Japan Meteorological Agency&amp;rsquo;s (JMA) forecast system (72% vs. 55%).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Delivered a compelling Proof of Concept (PoC) to MS&amp;amp;AD insurance group, showcasing practical applications and superior forecasting capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;transferable-skills&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transferable Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Analytical skills and Quantitative Analysis, Data visualization&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Geneartive AI&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Weather and Radar Meteorology.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leadership, project management, and problem-solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;responsibilities&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Led a data science team, ensuring collaboration between data scientists and industry experts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mentor the junior team members and support them with technical issues.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Translated specific needs of stakeholders into an optimized deep learning model.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;challenges-and-difficulties&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Challenges and Difficulties:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Required a deep understanding of meteorological data and generative deep learning techniques to provide accurate forecasts in a short time frame.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;feedback-and-endorsements&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feedback and Endorsements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Positive feedback from stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;context&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Context:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive background in deep learning and data analytics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Commitment to projects with direct business relevance, contributing to industry advancements.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return Forecasts using Conditional Autoconders</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/self-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/self-p2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:justify&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;relevance-to-the-business&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevance to the Business:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leveraged my expertise in Deep Learning to develope model for analyzing how hidden factors, which could be related to economic conditions, investor behavior, or other mysterious influences, affect asset returns.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The key benefits include reducing pricing errors and ensuring that the developed pricing model adheres to economic principles.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;accomplishments&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accomplishments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Developed and deployed an autoencoder model to generate accurate return forecasts, optimizing investment strategies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;transferable-skills&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transferable Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Proficient in financial data analysis and forecasting methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Skilled in applying Machine Learning techniques, especially Deep Learning models, to tabular data analysis.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;responsibilities&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Developed an autoencoder model for return forecast generation. Fine-tuning parameters for optimal performance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point Cloud Based 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/self-p5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/self-p5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:justify&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;relevance-to-the-business&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevance to the Business:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Leveraged my expertise in Computer Vision and Deep Learning to develop object detection algorithms using 3D cameras/sensors (3D Object Detection Algorithms). These advancements significantly enhance robustness, and capabilities of autonomous systems across wide ranges of applications and industries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Targeted applications could be&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Self-driving Cars: my algorithms help autonomous cars understand theirs surroundings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR): my algorithms facilitate the seamless integration of virtual objects into the physical world, elevating the user experience by providing realistic and immersive virtual environments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Industrial Automation: my algorithms can help to inspect components, detect infects automatically.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Medical diagnosis: my algorithms can be used for tasks such as tumor detection and organ segmentation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;accomplishments&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accomplishments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Two publications about algorithms for 3D object detection.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;transferable-skills&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transferable Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Solid Understanding of Computer Vision and Deep Learning models, 3D object modelling.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Skilled in Python and C++ programming; and utilization of tensorflow, Computer Vision&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;responsibilities&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Developed a prototype for 3D Object Detection systems, from conceptualization to implementation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionizing Newspaper Design: How AI is Automating Typesetting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:justify&#34;&gt;&#xA;&amp;emsp; The newsroom is a whirlwind of activity, with editors juggling deadlines, reporters chasing stories, and designers wrestling with stacks of paper and design software. Among these challenges, the process of typesetting – arranging articles, images, and advertisements on the page – stands out as a particularly time-consuming and labor-intensive task. But what if this critical step could be streamlined and enhanced with the power of artificial intelligence?&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  This post provide general information about an AI-based Typesetting system that I research and develop for MTI.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
