<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gitlab on Quang Chiem</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/gitlab/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gitlab on Quang Chiem</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/gitlab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Short-term Hail Nowcast Using AI for Extreme Weather Events</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/mti-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/mti-p2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevance to the Business:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leveraged my expertise in machine learning, deep learning, and data analytics to pioneer the development of an innovative AI-driven tool for short-term weather forecasting, with a specific focus on predicting hailstorms.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Targeted diverse spectrum of Japanese companies, primarily targeting the insurance and car dealership sectors, aimed at elevating risk assessment capabilities by providing exceptionally accurate forecasts. This enhancement in risk assessment holds particular significance for the insurance sector, where weather-related events can exert substantial financial implications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accomplishments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typesetting – AI-based Newspaper Placement Tool for the Japanese market.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/mti-p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lprojects/mti-p1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevance to the Business:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Applied machine learning, deep learning and data analytics expertise to develop a sophisticated typesetting tool.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Targeted specifically for Japanese newspapers, aimed at enhancing efficiency, quality of layout design and cost reduction.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accomplishments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Secured a patent for the Typesetting API.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Delivered a Proof of Concept (PoC) to renowned companies like Toshiba and Fujitsu.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transferable Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of state of the art machine learning methodologies and their business applications in python (sklearn, pytorch, flask, fastapi)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of IT and Cluster technologies: Docker, Gitlab.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Analytical skill, Data visualization, Constraint Programming and Deep Reinforcement Learning (Proximal Policy Optimization).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leadership, project management, and problem-solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Unpredictable: AI-Powered Weather Forecasting for Severe Events in Japan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/weather/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:justify&#34;&gt;&#xA;&amp;emsp; This project focuses on developing an advanced AI-based system for early detection of extreme weather events in Japan. By leveraging cutting-edge machine learning algorithms and analyzing vast amounts of historical weather data, this system aims to:&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improve accuracy and lead time:&lt;/strong&gt; Provide more accurate and timely predictions of severe weather events, such as intense rainfall, strong winds, and heavy snowfall.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhance early warning systems:&lt;/strong&gt; Empower weather information service providers to issue more precise and timely warnings to the public, allowing for swift evacuation and precautionary measures.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reduce human error:&lt;/strong&gt; Minimize the impact of human error in weather forecasting by automating data analysis and prediction processes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enable proactive risk management:&lt;/strong&gt; Equip individuals, businesses, and government agencies with the necessary information to proactively assess risks and implement effective mitigation strategies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;#demo&#34;&gt; &#xA;        &lt;button class=&#34;button&#34; style=&#34;color:red&#34;&gt;See demonstration !!!&lt;/button&gt; &#xA;    &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-key-benefits-of-this-ai-powered-weather-prediction-system&#34;&gt;I. Key benefits of this AI-powered weather prediction system&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Save lives:&lt;/strong&gt; Enable timely evacuations and reduce casualties during severe weather events.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimize property damage:&lt;/strong&gt; Allow for proactive measures to protect homes, businesses, and critical infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support informed decision-making:&lt;/strong&gt; Provide valuable data for emergency responders, disaster relief agencies, and government officials.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhance public awareness:&lt;/strong&gt; Raise public awareness about the dangers of severe weather and promote preparedness.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This project represents a significant step towards a more proactive and data-driven approach to weather forecasting in Japan. By harnessing the power of AI, we can build a more resilient and safer society, better prepared to face the challenges of the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
